Yuu?
Don't you need to hurry?
Coming!
You've got a bit sticking out in the back.
Shoot, really?
There, fixed it.
Thanks, Mom.
You're leaving a little earlier than usual.
It's the first day. I don't want to be late,
and I don't want to keep her waiting.
Tell Shikimori-san we said hello.
Sure.
Be careful.
Watch out for rocks, and cars,
and crows, and shingles...
I will. See you later.
Have a good day!
Ow, ow, ow...
Seriously? Already?
Hup!
Ow, ow, ow...
Ma'am, are you all right there?
Are you all right, young man?
Your hair's a mess.
I'm fine. Let me help you with that.
I made sure to fix my hair...
And all for nothing!
Shikimori-san!
Good morning, Shikimori-san.
Good morning, Izumi-san.
Look at her! She's so cute!
Wow, you're right! She looks like an idol!
Sorry I always keep you waiting.
Not at all. I enjoy waiting for you.
But that aside...
It looks like you had a rough
time again this morning.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm used to it.
My girlfriend is super cute,
but sometimes she's...
Not cute in the slightest...
Huh?!
I'm not cute?! That's so mean!
Sorry! I didn't mean to say it out loud!
That just makes it even worse!
Er, that's not what I meant...
Izumi-san!
That was close...
Sorry this stuff always happens.
You're not hurt, are you?
You don't need to apologize.
Sometimes, my girlfriend...
I swear... You gotta stop
worrying me so much.
...is incredibly cool.
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
#01  My Girlfriend Is Super Cute
They're in full bloom!
Aren't they beautiful?
Yeah.
They were beautiful during the
entrance ceremony last year, too.
Y-Yeah, they were.
I remember being so nervous that day.
I remember too, "Ijumi-san."
You can forget that part!
There! That's me!
Oh, everyone's already checking the board.
Indeed. There's quite a crowd.
Are you nervous, Izumi-san?
I am. We're about to find out
which class we're in.
God, please put me in class
with Shikimori-san again this year!
Please... Please!
Do you really need to pray that hard?
Well, I want to be in the same class as you!
Don't worry.
Even if we're in different classes,
I'll come visit you lots.
I love her!
Look, look! Right there!
Move over!
Look, look!
Outta the way!
Dude, same class!
Only Wears
Glasses in Class
20/20 Vision
Where's my name?
Class 4
Izumi Yuu
There it is! In Class 4!
And Shikimori-san, you're...
Shikimori
We're in the same class, Shikimori-san!
Look! It's right there!
Oh... So we are.
Thank you, God!
I look forward to studying
with you again this year.
Oh, likewise! Let's make it a good one.
Micchon!
Neko!
We're together again this year!
Hachimitsu, too!
Sup?
Let's take a pic!
Izumi!
Looks like we're in the same class again.
Inuzuka-kun!
You're in Class 4, too? That's great!
Looking forward to another year together.
Same.
Shikimori's with us, too, huh?
Yep.
Shikimori-san, I'll see you later, okay?
Okay.
I'm so glad we're in the same class.
But I got kinda carried away, didn't I?
Oh...
By the way, Shikimori-san,
when we go home today...
Heck, yeah!
Shikimori-san?
Looks like you flipped out
a little too soon, Micchon.
You're really on cloud nine.
The younger students will now
look up to you as their upperclassmen.
You'll most likely be the
central focus at school events.
Let's make this a fun year.
I'm sure not all of you are acquainted yet,
so let's start with some
quick introductions.
We'll go in seat number order,
so Izumi-kun, you're up first.
Yes, ma'am!
I'm Ijumi.
He blew it!
Today, I started my second year of high school.
Huh? What just happened?
It just kinda... went flying...
Shikimori-san, you never get angry, do you?
You're asking me that right now?
Sorry.
Today's Schedule
1. Opening Assembly
2. Class Opening Meeting
3. Homeroom
Th-Thanks...
Sure.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm just glad you weren't hurt.
Sorry this stuff always happens.
I-I'm going to the restroom to clean up!
Uh...
Izumi!
Look at you, showing off. I'm jealous, man.
Being naturally unlucky
must really suck, huh?
Where'd that eraser even come from, anyway?
Good question...
Better be careful.
Don't cause too much trouble for
that cute girlfriend of yours.
Yeah, she'd get tangled up
in your misfortune.
Why the heck is Shikimori-san
with Izumi, anyway?
Yeah, he's so dull.
I mean, so are we, but...
Damn, I'm so jealous!
Seriously, what's a guy gotta do
to get a girlfriend that cute?
I know, right?
Izumi-san, I'm back.
Oh, hey. Are you okay, Shikimori-san?
Yes.
Izumi-san, would you mind
accompanying me to the library for a bit?
Sure.
Uh-oh. I hope she didn't hear us.
Nah, we're probably fine.
That was scary!
But...
I-It was kinda awesome.
Peace and Harmony
Be Kind
to All
I might just be a little bit petty.
I wouldn't say that.
I don't think you need to worry
about what happened back there!
Huh?
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing...
My girlfriend is cute, but...
I'd really hate it if she were
hurt because of me.
Izumi!
Wanna go do something now that school's out?
You don't have work today, Inuzuka-kun?
Got the day off to celebrate the
start of a new school year!
Let's go, then.
That's my boy! You might look boring,
but you're down for anything!
Well, I've been thinking I want
to hang out with you more.
Oh, yeah?
I'll go let Shikimori-san know.
Okay.
Oh, you guys are going out, too?
We should all hang out together, then!
I guess we're all about
to become better friends.
Is that okay with you, Shikimori-san?
Yes! Of course!
This should be fun.
Y-Yeah, you're right...
Such innocence.
Even if we get an unasked-for tag-along.
You mean me?!
I could say the same about you two!
Loser has to treat whoever
gets the highest score.
Fine by me.
Count me out.
How spirited...
They sure are raring to go.
Have you ever bowled before, Shikimori-san?
Not very often. Two or three times, maybe.
Yeah, about the same for me.
But I'm looking forward to it.
I-I'll go get our balls!
Come with me, Inuzuka-kun!
Huh? Oh, sure.
Micchon!
This is your chance, girl.
My chance?
Don't play dumb.
You pretend to suck at bowling
and let your bae have all the glory!
My b-bae?
But pretending to be bad at it is just...
For girls, being bad at stuff
translates to cuteness.
All right! Let's get started!
I'm up first!
Woo-hoo!
Gah! Shoulda known I wouldn't get
a strike on the first throw!
Inu
Neko
He's pretty good...
Not bad.
Keep it down, Nekozaki.
Don't break the pins.
Hup!
So slow...
What the?!
Ayup.
That was awesome, Hachimitsu-san!
Shikimori-san?
Y-Yes?!
What's wrong?
Uh, nothing...
Maybe it would be better to go for cuteness...
I can't believe Hachimitsu got a strike.
That came outta nowhere.
Hmm? What'd you say?
You're up next, Izumi.
Oh, but...
Go on, Izumi-san.
Okay.
Think it'll stay on course?
Huh?
Now that was a real miracle!
Just too frickin' predictable!
The ball just curved on its own...
Neko
Hachimitsu
Izumi
Shikimori
You're up, Shikimori.
Micchon.
You know what to do, right?
You want your bae to think
you're cute, don't you?
Cute...
I want to hear that!
I want to hear him say I'm cute!
Shikimori-san!
You can do it!
Hey, check it out.
What's up?
She's about to get a perfect score.
Whoa, no way!
For real?! That's nuts!
Y-You gotta be kidding...
What is she, a monster?
Player
Inu
Neko
Hachimitsu
Izumi
Shikimori
Flawless       Victory
Th-That was so cool!
Izumi-san, hold up your hands!
L-Like this?
I did it!
She is seriously so cute!
All I see is the bold,
fearless smile of a powerhouse.
Just what is she?
I guess she chose looking cool
over looking cute.
See ya.
Bye-bee!
Adieu.
Oh, I almost forgot.
The loser was supposed to treat
the highest scorer, right?
Oh, you don't have to do that.
But...
In that case, please walk home with me.
Huh? But we always do that...
That's why I want it.
W-Wow, it's so windy!
It's messing up your hair!
Well, you should see yours!
There have been a lot of empty cans
and things blowing around...
straight at you.
Sorry.
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
How did she stop that newspaper from
hitting me without even looking?
Incredible.
Thanks, Shikimori-san. I really
am sorry this stuff always happens.
Aren't I always telling you
that you don't need to apologize?
Oh, sorry— Er...
I've gotten used to this kind of thing.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, but I feel pathetic when you
have to protect me all the time.
RAKA
Corp.
Shikimori-san?
Did it bother you when those
guys in class were teasing you?
Well, no... What they said was true, after all.
I really don't do a thing for you.
At this rate, I'll...
Izumi-san...
All you need to do is stay by my side.
It doesn't matter to me what people may say.
I'm going to keep protecting you
because I want to.
My girlfriend is so incredibly cool.
And for that...
I'm in love.
I-Is this really the time to say that?!
Oh, you're not hurt, are you?
Is your foot okay?
Huh?!
Uh, y-yes! It's just fine!
You were amazing just now!
It was almost like... like...
It was just a coincidence! Pure coincidence!
Really?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Huh?
Yes, I'm sure! I'm absolutely fine!
What about you? Are you all right?
I'm totally fine, thanks to you.
That's a relief!
SEE YOU~